

POPICA ANDREI

Age 26 from Bucuresti, not married

Contact details

■ andrei.popica@yahoo.com

+40767453557

♀ sector 3

About me

I'm an objective person who like to think logical or to see the logical in things. The 8 years of real-profile studies (High school Mathematics-Informatics and Faculty of Constructions) helped me develop an analyte thinking. On professional side so far, i have activated in areas where i put in practice the knowledge accumulated and have acquired some new ones.

Other passions: psychology, which helps me a lot understanding with other people and how to interact with them.

Professional experience

Experience by departments Engineering : 10 months

Administrative / Logistics: 1 year and 11 months

Construction / Facilities : 4 months Marketing: 1 year and 7 months

Jan 2019 - Jul 2020

Data entry | Marketing Assistant | Image Editor - Zenda Outlet

1 year and 7 months

Bucharest | Marketing | Commerce / Retail

I take care of the marketing part (Helping the Specialist), doing the following things:-Facebook Ads, administrating the Instagram page, Keeping track of spending and budgets. I take care of everything that means product that appears on the site (prices, categories, etc).

Also, on the graphics side i make the banners that the site needs.

Microsoft Office Photoshop Microsoft Excel

Oct 2017 - Jul 2018

Technical Sketch/Construction engineer - Fdp Pro Cons SRL

10 months

Bucharest | Engineering | Construction

Structural design (resistance calculations).

Preparation of execution plans

Jan 2017 - Apr 2017

Technician - Accuro

4 months

Bucharest | Construction / Facilities | Construction

AutoCAD

7/2/2020

CV Popica Andrei eJobs.ro - cel mai mare portal de recrutare online din Romania cu peste 4 mil de CV-uri.

Jan 2015 - Nov 2016

Administrator - Camin Studentes Giulesti

1 year and 11 months

Bucharest | Administrative / Logistics | Administrative / Public Sector

During the faculty, I was the manager of this home, dealing with all the problems that occurred in the course of time. These include: Paying bills, managing money, maintaining a pleasant environment, repairing objects.

Education

2013 - 2017

Bachelor's degree - UTCB

FCCIA | Bucuresti

♣ Skills

General skills

Wordpress	Python	JavaScript	css	HTML5

Skills from work experience

Microsoft Office	Photoshop	Microsoft Excel	AutoCAD
------------------	-----------	-----------------	---------

♣ Foreign languages

English - Medium

Published work

https://cusidesprecalatorii.wordpress.com acquired on May 2020

Certifications

Codecademy -JavaScript period Mar 2020 - May 2020

Python Fundamentals - Bit Academy acquired on Jan 2020

CodeBerry Programing School period Jul 2019 - Sep 2019

Projects

GitHub

acquired on Jan 2020

https://github.com/Andrew9426

Hobbies

Passion for Psychology, Reading, Travels, Sport

Driving license

Category B acquired on 15 Jun 2012